https://www.usjersey.com/legal-disclosures/online-privacy-statement.aspx

Policy: Undesirable Genetic Factors
Designated Carriers:
Rules: National Jersey Jug Futurity
The Jersey (Bonnie Mohr)
NAJ
About National All-Jersey Inc.
Policy: Undesirable Genetic Factors
Designated Carriers:
Rules: National Jersey Jug Futurity
The Jersey (Bonnie Mohr)
NAJ
About National All-Jersey Inc.
Online Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the American Jersey Cattle Association and National All-Jersey Inc. (known as AJCA-NAJ) and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to AJCA-NAJ include www.usjersey.com, usjersey.com subdirectory websites, jerseybid.com, queenofquality.com and infojersey.com. By using the AJCA-NAJ website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of Your Personal Information
AJCA-NAJ may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name, address and other non-financial personally identifiable information. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by AJCA-NAJ. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the AJCA website.
AJCA-NAJ encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from American Jersey Cattle Association and National All-Jersey Inc. so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. AJCA-NAJ is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the AJCA-NAJ website.
Use of Your Personal Information
AJCA-NAJ collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.
AJCA-NAJ may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from AJCA-NAJ and its affiliates. AJCA-NAJ may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new programs and services that may be offered.
AJCA-NAJ does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
AJCA-NAJ may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to AJCA-NAJ, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
AJCA-NAJ will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on AJCA-NAJ or the sites; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of AJCA-NAJ; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of AJCA-NAJ, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The AJCA-NAJ website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize AJCA-NAJ pages, or register with AJCA-NAJ site or services, a cookie helps American Jersey Cattle Association and National All-Jersey Inc. to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same AJCA-NAJ website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the AJCA-NAJ features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the AJCA-NAJ programs and services or websites you visit.
Security of Your Personal Information
AJCA-NAJ secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.
Children Under Thirteen
AJCA-NAJ does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
Opt-Out & Unsubscribe
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from AJCA-NAJ by contacting us here:
Email: info@usjersey.com
Web page: www.usjersey.com
Phone: 614-861-3636
Changes to this Statement
AJCA-NAJ will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. AJCA-NAJ encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how AJCA-NAJ is protecting your information.
Contact Information
AJCA-NAJ welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that AJCA-NAJ has not adhered to this Statement, please contact AJCA-NAJ at:
American Jersey Cattle Association
National All-Jersey Inc.
6486 East Main Street
Reynoldsburg, Ohio 43068
Email Address:
info@usjersey.com
Telephone number:
614-861-3636
Effective as of August 31, 2017
© 2020 American Jersey Cattle Association and National All-Jersey Inc.
6486 East Main Street
Reynoldsburg, Ohio 43068-2362 U.S.A.
We make owning Jerseys more profitable.
